[
    {
        "question": "How many hours are there in a day?",
        "answers": ["6", "12", "24", "Not enough"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the anime series 'Sonic X', how many Chaos Emeralds are there?",
        "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "Iconic Fate series character Saber is who?",
        "answers": ["King Arthur", "King John", "King Richard", "King Henry"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [1, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Japanese city do you find the district of Akihabara, home to a large selection of anime and manga merchandise?",
        "answers": ["Osaka", "Kyoto", "Fukuoka", "Tokyo"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [1, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following countries does not make an appearance on the anime series 'Hetalia'?",
        "answers": ["Austria", "Hungary", "Poland", "Vatican City"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "What anime series involves the 'Endless Eight' saga, which involves an endless time loop that lasts eight episodes?",
        "answers": ["Lucky Star", "School Days", "Ouran High School Host Club", "Haruhi Suzumiya"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [1, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wears glasses in the anime series Nichijou?",
        "answers": ["Mr. Sakamoto", "Mio", "Yuuko", "Mai"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "By replacing the last letter of the drink with a specific vowel, which of these alcoholic drinks becomes the surname of a 'Jojo's Bizarre Adventure' character?",
        "answers": ["Brandy", "Sake", "Tequila", "Vodka"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many live action versions of 'Assassination Classroom' are there?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Originally, the game 'Donkey Kong' featuring Mario was supposed to contain characters from what other cartoon series?",
        "answers": ["Tom and Jerry", "Popeye", "Flash Gordon", "Beetle Bailey"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "On the anime series 'Cardcaptor Sakura', which of the following is not the name of a card that Sakura Kinomoto captures?",
        "answers": ["Shot", "Steal", "Snow", "Sweet"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Zatch Bell's evil twin brother?",
        "answers": ["Dubois", "Zeno", "Xue", "Robert"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "Until 1917, what city was the capital of the Russian Empire?",
        "answers": ["Novogrod", "St. Petersburg", "Vladivostok", "Smolensk"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the fate of Generals Montcalm and Wolfe, who led the French and British forces at the Battle of the Plains of Abraham in 1759?",
        "answers": ["Only Montcalm died", "Only Wolfe died", "Both generals survived", "Both generals died"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first name of Roman Catholic pope Pius XII, who reigned from March 1939 to October 1958?",
        "answers": ["Eugenio", "Giovanni", "Giuseppe", "Angelo"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [1, 2]
    }
]